A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1934-1936
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- General Files, 1934-1936
  - "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous Y.W.C.A.--recommendation; Zeta Pi--loss of renters) 1934-1936 (Box 23)